高音
主唱
低音
中音
那天我在街上闲逛的时候
While strolling through the park one day
翻译，特效，压制：布尔
字体：思源宋体 SemiBold
正是欢乐的五月份
It was in the merry month of May
我意外地迷恋上了
I was taken by surprise
一双调皮的眼睛
By a pair of roguish eyes
在那一瞬间我可怜的心被偷走了
In a moment my poor heart was stole away
她不过是冲我微笑了一下
A smile was all she gave to me
注：这句是原视频简介里就标出来的，
我不太清楚是什么意思
[soft-shoe break]
当然我们都很开心
Of course we were as happy as can be
[soft-shoe break]
我马上举起了帽子
I immediately raised my hat
她害羞地回应
She responded with a shy remark
而我永远也不该忘记
And I never shall forget
那个美妙的下午
That lovely afternoon
注：这首歌原名是The Fountain in the Park
我和她在公园里的喷泉相遇
When I met her at the fountain in the park